bigspaceship.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy | Big Spaceship | DUMBO, NYC

This is the web site of Big Spaceship LLC (“Big Spaceship,” “we” or “us”).

Big Spaceship has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy with respect to the Sites (as defined below), as well as services we provide to our clients (“Client Services”). This privacy policy explains our data collection and use practices for the Site and our Client Services.

By using or accessing the websites we administer, which are located at bigspaceship.com, bigspaceship.net, bigspaceship.org, bigspaceship.biz, bigspaceship.us, bigspaceship.info, bigspaceship.agency, bigspaceship.marketing, bigspaceship.wtf, spaceship.wtf, spaceship.agency, spcshp.it, spcshp.net, spcshp.in, spcshp.info, spcshp.org, spcshp.co, spcshp.us, spcshp.tv, themostawesomethingever.com, throned.tv (collectively, the “Sites”), you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE SITES.

The Site provides information about the company, products, services and a means to contact Big Spaceship.

Our postal address is:  
Big Spaceship LLC  
45 Main Street, Suite 716  
Brooklyn, NY 11201

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy@bigspaceship.com](mailto:privacy@bigspaceship.com), or you can reach us by telephone at [718-222-0281](tel:718-222-0281).

##### TECHNOLOGIES WE USE TO COLLECT INFORMATION

We may use cookies, log files and web beacons on the Sites and in Client Services. We often engage or cooperate with service and technology companies to collect this information and use it in Client Services.

Cookies are small files that a Site transfers to the hard drive of a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies are “persistent” in that they remain on your hard drive until deleted. Other cookies are “temporary” in that they are removed when you leave the site or close your browsing session.

Log files track actions occurring on websites and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed.

Web beacons are electronic files used to track your navigation of a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.

##### WHAT INFORMATION DO WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information._ Some non-PII may automatically be collected as you browse the Sites and use Client Services. Web servers we use may automatically collect information sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” such as the domain name of the service providing you with Internet access, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your browser type and version, operating system and platform, the average time spend on the Sites, pages viewed, information searched for, access times and other relevant statistics. We may use cookies, web beacons and log files to collect this information. Your Internet browser stores Client Services-related data as cookies in some cases as well. If you have cookies disabled, if you delete your cookies, or if other software deletes the cookies used for that data storage, such data is permanently lost because it is not retained separately by us.

_Personally Identifiable Information._ In order to take advantage of certain features of the Sites and Client Services, we may ask you to provide your first name, last name, e-mail address or other information about yourself to help you use the Sites and Client Services (collectively, “PII”). You are not required to provide us with this information, but if you choose not to, you may not be able to participate in some of the activities on the Sites or Client Services. The only way we receive your PII is through your voluntary disclosure of it.

_Information Collected from Other Sources._ We may license and otherwise obtain non-PII from various other companies, including research companies, data aggregation companies and other third party companies. Data sets may include information about you or your demographic segment that such companies have licensed, purchased or collected. We use this information for all the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and for any other lawful purpose that we choose.

_Information Collected By Third Parties._ Some of the services and advertisements included via the Site and our Client Services, as well as sites that the Client Services link to, are delivered or served by third-party companies. These companies may place or recognize cookies, web beacons, or other technology to track certain personal and non-PII about users. We do not have access, nor control over, third party use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used. You should check the applicable privacy polices of such third-party sites and services you visit to determine how they handle any information they collect from you.

##### WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER?

_Service Participation._ We may use the information we collect from you to allow you to participate in the Sites’ and Client Services’ activities for which the information is collected, including, but not limited to, to improve the content of the respective Sites and Client Services, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, to notify users about updates to the Sites or Client Services and for our internal contact database purposes. In some cases, Client Services we develop may allow you to connect data you have already provided through another services (e.g., Google, Facebook, Twitter or Paypal) to such Client Services. When we develop this sort of connection, we do not locally store or process any of your data; rather, we connect the third-party service directly with the Client Service you are accessing, which is hosted through a third party with which we have no, or limited, contact. Some of our Client Services may provide e-commerce solutions that allow you to purchase goods and services online. Although we develop the means by which financial information may be collected from these services, we do not store or process any information from your financial transactions.

_Statistical Analysis._ We may perform statistical, demographic and marketing analysis regarding users and their patterns in using the Sites and Client Services. We use this information for analytical purposes, the results of which we may offer in aggregated, anonymous form to our clients. We may use cookies in Client Services to estimate the total reach of an advertising campaign, control the delivery of certain content and generally improve your online experience with respect to the Site and the Client Services we provide.

##### WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE GATHER?

Any communication or material you transmit to us by email or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions, or the like is, and will be treated as, non-confidential and nonproprietary. We may disclose such information to our clients and affiliates for commercial purposes.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may disclose information we collect as follows:

_Within the Company._ We may use information that we collect or that you provide internally, through Big Spaceship or its parent, subsidiaries, successors, assigns or affiliates, which may change if we acquire, or are acquired by, another company.

_To Third Parties._ We may disclose your information to third parties (including our clients, technology partners, publishers and administrative service providers) for purposes elsewhere described in this policy, as well as research, data validation, aggregation, enhancement, verification, suppression, marketing, advertising and other lawful purposes in providing Client Services. Such information does not include PII unless you voluntarily provided it in a form that was expressly designated as part of a commercial survey or an online form. We do not take responsibility for any third-party entities referenced in this paragraph, which may have privacy policies different than this Privacy Policy.

_As Required by Law._ We may disclose information we collect, including PII, to third parties as required or permitted by law. For example, we may disclose information:  
to regulators; and to law enforcement authorities pursuant to official requests; to service providers who perform legal compliance services for us.

##### WHEN MAY WE CONTACT YOU WITH THE INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE?

By providing your email address to us, you expressly consent to receive emails. We may use email to communicate with you, to send information that you have requested or to send information about other products or services developed or provided by us or our clients; provided, however, that we will not give your email address to another party to promote their products or services directly to you.

_CAN-SPAM Act of 2003._ We will not send you marketing messages if you have opted out of them. You may opt out of email or other communication at any time by sending an email to [privacy@bigspaceship.com](mailto:privacy@bigspaceship.com). We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes without your permission.

_Service-Related Email._ If you choose to sign up for a newsletter administered by Big Spaceship, you may elect to sign up for third party mailings or announcements through the newsletter. Whether you choose to receive these mailings or announcements is your choice. If you choose to receive them from a specific source, you will receive commercial messages from independent third parties over whom we have no control and who each have their own privacy policies that you should review. You may typically remove your email address from these third party lists by following the instructions on emails that you receive. We do not take responsibility for third-party companies who contact you by email at your direction.

##### HOW DO I CHANGE, REQUEST OR UPDATE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You may update information you provide us or ask for a copy of it by contacting us directly at [privacy@bigspaceship.com](mailto:privacy@bigspaceship.com).

##### MISCELLANEOUS

_COPPA Compliance._ The Site is not intended for use by persons under the age of 13 and we do not employ advertising targeted towards children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from or about children under the age of 13. If you believe that your child has submitted PII to our Site and you would like to request that such information be deleted, you may do so by emailing [privacy@bigspaceship.com](mailto:privacy@bigspaceship.com). Further, in accordance with law, when a visitor files a complaint online and indicates an age under 13, no personally identifying information will be collected in conjunction with that submission. You can learn more about COPPA at the United States Federal Trade Commission Website: <https://www.ftc.gov/tips-advice/business-center/privacy-and-security/children%27s-privacy>

_California Privacy Rights._ Under the California “Shine the Light” law, California residents may opt-out of a company’s disclosure of PII to third parties for its direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, you may choose to opt-out of our sharing of your PII with third parties for marketing purposes at any time by submitting a request to us by email or phone. It is important to note that this opt-out does not prohibit disclosures made for non-marketing purposes.

_Safe Harbor Data Privacy Notice._ In the U.S., we comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework published by the U.S. Department of Commerce (the “Safe Harbor Principles”) with respect to PII it receives from the European Union and Switzerland. The Company has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. This notice outlines the Company’s general policy and practices in compliance with the Safe Harbor Principles, including the type of information to which this notice applies, how we use information, and your choices regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, your PII. For purposes of this notice, “personally identifiable information” or “PII” includes information (a) transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States; (b) recorded in any form by us; and (c) pertaining to a specific individual who is identified in, or is identifiable from, the data. This notice applies to all PII we handle, including online (except as noted below), off-line, and manually processed data. If there is any conflict between this Privacy Policy and the Safe Harbor Principles, the Safe Harbor Principles will apply. If you would like to learn more about the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks, please visit <http://export.gov/safeharbor>.

_Notice and Choice._ We obtain PII only as permitted by the Safe Harbor Principles or with the consent of the individual affected. We may ask for your consent to collect, use, and/or disclose PII in certain ways, and you may be required to give your consent in order to use our services. To the extent permitted under the Safe Harbor Principles, we reserve the right to process PII in the course of providing services through the Service without the knowledge of individuals involved. If you wish to opt out of our collection or our disclosure of PII to third parties, you may contact us at [privacy@bigspaceship.com](mailto:privacy@bigspaceship.com) with a request to do so. The request should include your name, email address, login information, and any specifics that may help us to prevent the collection of PII you do not wish to have collected or disclosed. Please note that if you opt out of our data collection practices, the Service may be less functional for you.

_Transfers._ Big Spaceship will obtain assurances from its affiliates that they will safeguard PII consistently with this Privacy Policy. If we learn that an affiliate is using or disclosing PII in a manner contrary to this Privacy Policy, we will take steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. Transfers of information permitted under this notice, either to third parties or amongst the Company and its affiliates, may include the transfer of data from one jurisdiction to another, such as transfers to and from the United States of America, the UK and Australia.

_Security & Enforcement._ Big Spaceship will take reasonable precautions to protect PII in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction, and it will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Privacy Policy. We try to keep the information we collect from you as current as possible, and we take steps to maintain the security of your PII and to prevent unauthorized access to it by those who do not have a legitimate need for it. To that end, we periodically review our security measures. We cannot guarantee, in every circumstance, the security of the PII you provide through the Services. All incoming encrypted information is routed through our firewall, which serves as a gatekeeper for our system. Only data containing the correct authorization is permitted past the firewall. Attempts to pass the firewall are constantly monitored for suspicious activity.

_Reasonable Access._ We will provide you reasonable access to PII that you provide through the Website and the reasonable ability to review and correct it, as applicable, to the extent providing such access and means to review and correct:

(a) are not outweighed, in our sole discretion, by the burden of providing of it; or  
(b) are otherwise impracticable for any reason.

By using our Website you consent to our collection and use of your PII as described in this policy. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this Website, and your continued use constitutes acceptance of those changes. Thank you for visiting our Website, and for taking the time to read this policy.

Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, or the breach thereof, shall be settled by arbitration administered by the JAMS Safe Harbor Program in accordance with its Commercial or other Arbitration Rules, and judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator(s) may be entered in any court having jurisdiction thereof.

The operator of the Sites is Big Spaceship Inc. Big Spaceship may find it appropriate or necessary, or may be legally obligated, to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page and update the effective date (found at the bottom) so that you have a way to always become aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. For changes to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent (if we have the necessary contact information) before implementing such revisions with respect to such information, or notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our website or by directly sending you a notification. For all other changes, it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often.

YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT BIG SPACESHIP’S LIABILITY FROM ANY DISPUTE OVER PRIVACY OR THIS PRIVACY POLICY WILL BE LIMITED AS SET FORTH IN THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF OUR APPLICABLE WEBSITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, WHICH ARE INCORPORATED BY THIS REFERENCE.

EFFECTIVE DATE: February 1st, 2015
